export const jsQuizz = {
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
        choices: [
          "Virtual DOM",
          "Original DOM",
          "Both A and B",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Virtual DOM",
      },
      {
        question: "What is ReactJS?",
        choices: [
          "Server-side framework",
          "User Interface framework",
          "both a and b",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "User Interface framework",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside",
        choices: ["Render with arguments", "setState", "PropTypes", "props"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "props",
      },
      {
        question: "In which language is React.js written?",
        choices: ["Python", "Java", "C#", "JavaScript"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "JavaScript",
      },
      {
        question: "What is Babel?",
        choices: [
          "JavaScript interpreter",
          "JavaScript transpiler",
          "JavaScript compiler",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "JavaScript transpiler",
      },
      {
        question: "What is a state in React?",
        choices: [
          "A permanent storage",
          "Internal storage of the component",
          "External storage of the component",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Internal storage of the component",
      },
      {
        question: "What are props in React?",
        choices: [
          "Props are arguments passed into React components",
          "Props are used to store component data",
          "Props are a way to style components",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Props are arguments passed into React components",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the purpose of a key prop?",
        choices: [
          "To uniquely identify elements in the DOM",
          "To store component data",
          "To pass arguments to components",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "To uniquely identify elements in the DOM",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the use of the useEffect hook in React?",
        choices: [
          "To manage side effects in functional components",
          "To handle component state",
          "To create context",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "To manage side effects in functional components",
      },
      {
        question: "What does JSX stand for?",
        choices: [
          "JavaScript XML",
          "JavaScript Extension",
          "Java Syntax eXtension",
          "Java Source XML",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "JavaScript XML",
      },
    ],
  };
  
  export const resultInitalState = {
    score: 0,
    correctAnswers: 0,
    wrongAnswers: 0,
  };
